

JESUS VALADEZ

WEB PROGRAMMER

CONTACT

- +55 1299 6882
- ☑ JESUSVALADEZF@OUTLOOK.COM
- HTTPS://JESUSVAL.GITHUB.IO/RESUME

PROFILE

II'm a full-stack developer from Guadalajara, with 2 years of experience designing, developing, and implementing web and mobile applications. I'm looking to join a team to continue to grow up my skill set while contributing to the development of the team.

EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- Designing new solutions and implementing new solutions to optimize internal process.
- Give maintenance to applications and generate new
- functionalities.

FULL STACK DEVELOPER JR AGILGOB | JUN 2020 - DEC 2020

• Developing new functionalities to optimize user experience in private government web platforms as modifying functions to increase security.

BACKEND DEVELOPER INTERN ITESO | JAN 2020 - JUN 2020

• Developing a backend platform to communicate climate monitor sensor web to a website to analyze climate log.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SYSTEM ENGINEERING

ITESO | 2015 - 2020

SKILLS

• Laravel	••••
• React	••••
React Native	••••
• SQL	••••
• API Rest	••••
Responsive design	••••
Agile methodologies	••••